GABRIELE G. FALLOON

San Antonio, TX 78255 | Phone: 214-929-1872 | Email: ggfalloon@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/gabriele-falloon | Github: github.com/ggfalloon |Portfolio: ggfalloon.github.io/Portfolio/

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Full Stack Web Developer with a background of high-quality reporting, sales and software maintenance. Recently known for clean, effective coding and successful team collaboration. An innovative, goal-driven, organized and energetic professional.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages/Frameworks: HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript/JQuery, Bootstrap, JSON, AJAX/API **Other:** Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Git, Terminal, Microsoft Office, Google Suite, Zoom, Hangouts

PROJECTS

Better Weather - ggfalloon.github.io/BETTER-WEATHER/ | github/ggfalloon/BETTER-WEATHER **2020** Worked with a team of 3 to produce a mobile-first web app that provides odds data, outdoor conditions and stadium information appealing to the user who wishes to place an informed wager on NFL football games.

 Tools used: HTML5, TailwindCSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX: OpenWeather API (provides live weather data), The Odds API (provides live odds data), Wikipedia API (provides table array of stadium details)

JavaScript Code Quiz - ggfalloon.github.io/CodeQuiz/ | github.com/ggfalloon/CodeQuiz 2020

A fun and interactive quiz to test your knowledge of Javascript. This program allows you to record your initials, score, clear scores or play again.

• Tools used: HTML5/CSS3, Bootstrap CSS, JavaScript

• Tools used: HTML5/CSS3, Bootstrap CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Moment.js

EXPERIENCE

Elevate Bartending, Austin, TX — Director of Events

2018 - 2020

- Remotely managed all incoming leads and often converted over 30% to bookings.
- Assisted in development and maintenance of the company's new website. Using Google Sheets, created and maintained essential spreadsheets for tracking sales records, payroll, events, etc.
- Contributed to 600% growth in sales in the first year of employment.
- Detailed events for both Austin and San Antonio locations and led execution of San Antonio events.

Legacy Church, Plano, TX — Office Manger/Church Clerk

2012 - 20

- Maintained and updated software database. Improved and developed various Excel reports.
- Managed/recruited volunteers, on-boarded new staff, supply budget, organized events, calendars & phone systems. Led initiative to reduce energy costs through wifi enabled programmable thermostats.

Hudson & Marshall of Texas. Plano. TX — Account Lead

2007 - 2011

- Promoted to Contract Administrator within 3 months of initial hire date.
- Received a second promotion to Account Lead as liaison for the company's servicing clients. Assisted
 in developing essential client reporting using Excel's macro and pivot table functions.
- Attended multiple real estate auctions throughout the country, completing various tasks to ensure smooth transactions for buyers, investors and real estate agents.

EDUCATION

University of Texas at San Antonio, Bootcamp Certificate in Full Stack Web Development Richland College, Dallas, TX Microcomputer Applications
Stephen F. Austin State University, Nacogdoches, TX General Business

AFFILIATIONS

Association for Computing Machinery, Student Member